A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Education, 2006-2014 (bulk 2009-2013)
Library of Virginia
- IV. Legislative Files, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)., Extent: 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes).
  - General Assembly - House Bills: 1806-2264 2011 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - General Assembly House Bill 2311-Senate Bill 1362 2011 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Higher Education Opportunity Act 2010-2011 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Health and Human Resources (HHR) 2013 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - House Appropriations Committee Retreat 2013 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - K-12 Education 2011-2013 (1 of 5) (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - K-12 Education 2011-2013 (2 of 5) (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - K-12 Education 2011-2013 (3 of 5) (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - K-12 Education 2011-2013 (4 of 5) (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - K-12 Education 2011-2013 (5 of 5) (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - K-12 Education Reform 2011 (1 of 6) (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - K-12 Education Reform 2011 (2 of 6) (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - K-12 Education Reform 2011 (3 of 6) (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - K-12 Education Reform 2011 (4 of 6) (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - K-12 Education Reform 2011 (5 of 6) (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - K-12 Education Reform 2012 (6 of 6) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Office of the Inspector General 2012-2013 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Opportunity Education Institute 2013 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Opportunity to Learn 2010-2012 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Opportunity to Learn 2010-2012 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Regulations 2013 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Re-Entry Housing 2010 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - School Start Initiative 2011 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Session Enrolled Bill Reviews 2011 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - SB 966 - P.E. Bill 2011 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Strategic Compensation 2011-2013 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Teacher Contracts 2011 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Teacher Contracts 2013 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Teacher Contracts 2013 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Virginia High School League (VHSL) Subcommittee - HB 2395 2011 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 2010 Governor's Policy 2010 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 2011 Legislative Action Summaries (LAS): HB 1416-1748 2011 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - 2011 Legislative Action Summaries (LAS): HB 1775-2378 2011 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - 2011 Legislative Action Summaries (LAS): SB 744-1363 2011 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - 2011 Legislative Action Summaries (LAS): General 2011 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - 2011 Proposals 2011 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - 2011 Proposals 2011 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - 2012 Proposals 2012 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - 2013 Agency Proposed 2013 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - 2013 Agency Proposed 2013 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - 2013 Legislative Action Summaries (LAS): HB 1309-1582 2012-2013 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - 2013 Legislative Action Summaries (LAS): HB 1557-1976 2012-2013 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - 2013 Legislative Action Summaries (LAS): HB 1999-2322 2013 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - 2013 Legislative Action Summaries (LAS): SB 981-1171 2013 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - 2013 Legislative Action Summaries (LAS): SB 1175-1940 2013 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - 2014 Proposals - Department of Education 2013-2014 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - 2014 Proposals - Department of Education 2014 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - 2014 Proposals - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 2013-2014 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - 2014 Proposals - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 2013-2014 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - 2014 Proposals - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 2014 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - 2014 Proposals - University of Virginia (UVA) 2013-2014 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - 2014 Proposals - Virginia Military Institute (VMI) 2013-2014 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- V. Budget and Planning, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)., Extent: 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes).
  This series documents budgetary, grant, and contract planning activities and initiatives related to education of all levels during Governor McDonnell's tenure. This includes presentations, grant proposals and drafts, contracts, budgetary plans and legislation. For more budget related material, also see Series IV. Legislative Initiatives, 2010-2014.
  - Budget Concerns 2013-2014 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Debt Capacity 2010 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Grants - Capital Region 2010 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Grants - Long Range Vision 2011 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Grants - Strategic Compensation 2013 (1 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Grants - Strategic Compensation 2013 (2 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Grants - Strategic Compensation 2013 (2 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Grants - George Mason University (GMU) 2012 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Grants - James Madison University (JMU) 2012 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Grants - University of Mary Washington 2012 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Higher Education 2011 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - House Appropriations and Senate Finance 2013 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - House Appropriations and Senate Finance 2013 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - K-12 2011 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - K-12 Governor's Briefing 2012 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Overviews 2010 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Pre-Session Process and Agency Legislation 2013 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Presentation-Senate Finance 2010 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Public Broadcasting Contracts 2010-2012 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Public Education - Direct Aid 2010-2012 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Race to the Top 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Race to the Top 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Regulation Review 2010 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Senate Finance Committee - Tuition 2013 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Senate Finance Committee - Tuition 2013 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Commission for the Arts 2011-2012 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - General 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - James Madison University (JMU) 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - University of Mary Washington 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Old Dominion University (ODU) 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - University of Virginia (UVA) 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - University of Virginia (UVA) Wise 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - George Mason University (GMU) 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Christopher Newport University (CNU) 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Norfolk State University (NSU) 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Richard Bland University 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia Military Institute (VMI) 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Institute of Marine Science 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia State University (VSU) 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - William and Mary 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia Tech 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia Community College System (VCCS) 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Radford University 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Longwood University 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Christopher Newport University (CNU) 2011 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - William and Mary 2011 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - George Mason University (GMU) 2011 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - James Madison University (JMU) 2011 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Norfolk State University (NSU) 2011 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Old Dominion University (ODU) 2011 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Richard Bland University 2011 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - University of Mary Washington 2011 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - University of Virginia (UVA) 2011 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - University of Mary Washington 2011 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia Community College System (VCCS) 2011 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU) 2011 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU) 2012-2013 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU) 2012-2013 (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia Military Institute (VMI) 2011 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia State University (VSU) 2011 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia Tech 2011 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Six Year Plans - Colleges - Virginia Tech Co-Op and Agriculture 2011 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 2010 Session Materials 2010 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 2011 Session Material 2011 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 2013 Budget Proposals 2013 (1 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 2013 Budget Proposals 2013 (2 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 2013 Budget Proposals 2013 (3 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 2013 Budget Proposals 2013 (4 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 2014 Budget Proposals 2014 (1 of 5) (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - 2014 Budget Proposals 2014 (2 of 5) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - 2014 Budget Proposals 2014 (3 of 5) (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - 2014 Budget Proposals 2014 (4 of 5) (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - 2014 Budget Proposals 2014 (5 of 5) (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - 2014-2016 Budget Outlook 2013 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- VI. Decision Briefs and Supporting Documents, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)., Extent: 1 cu. ft. (1 box).
  This series is arranged in original chronological order. A bulk of the series includes correspondence. Also see Series III: Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, 2010-2014.
  - March-June 2010 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - June-August 2010 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - August-October 2010 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - November 2010 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - December 2010 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - January-April 2011 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - April-July 2011 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - August-September 2011 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - November-December 2011 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - February-March 2012 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - March-May 2012 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Level II Memoranda of Understanding 2011 (Box 15, Folder 35)